const maths = {
  level1Mat: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'What is the equation for sloping lines?',
      selection: ['y = mx + c', 'm = y + cx', 'cx = m + y', 'y = cx + m'],
      answer: 'y = mx + c',
      description: 'The equation of a straight line on a graph is made up of a y term, an x term, and a number and are written in the form of y = mx + c. The slope of the line is known as the gradient and is represented by m in the equation. The point at which the line crosses the y-axis is the c in the equation.'
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Which way does a positive gradient slope?',
      selection: ['Left', 'Right', 'Up', 'Down'],
      answer: 'Right',
      description: 'Direction is important when it comes to determining slope. It’s important to pay attention to whether you are moving up, down, left, or right; that is, if you are moving in a positive or negative direction. If you go up to get to your second point, the rise is positive. If you go down to get to your second point, the rise is negative. If you go right to get to your second point, the run is positive. If you go left to get to your second point, the run is negative.'
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'What is the equation for vertical lines?',
      selection: ['k = x', 'c = x', 'x = k', 'x = c'],
      answer: 'x = k',
      description: 'The equation of a vertical line always takes the form x=k. Where k is any number and k is also the x-intercept.'
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'How is theoretical probability calculated?',
      selection: ['P = num of favourable outcomes/num of possible outcomes', 'It doesnt need to be calculated', 'P = num of possible outcomes/num of favourable outcomes', 'P = num of favourable outcomes/num of trials'],
      answer: 'P = num of favourable outcomes/num of possible outcomes',
      description: 'Theoretical Probability can be calculated because each outcome has the same chance of occuring. Therefore P = number of favourable outcomes/number of possible outcomes '
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'What should the probability on each group of branches on a probability tree equal?',
      selection: ['One', 'Two', 'Three', 'Four'],
      answer: 'One',
      description: 'Sometimes you don’t know whether to multiply or add probabilities. A probability tree makes it easier to figure out when to add and when to multiply. By multiplying along the branches and adding probabilities down the columns the result should always be 1.'
    }
  ],
  level2Mat: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    }
  ],
  level3Mat: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'What is the equation for sloping lines?',
      selection: ['y = mx + c', 'm = y + cx', 'cx = m + y', 'y = cx + m'],
      answer: 'y = mx + c',
      description: 'The equation of a straight line on a graph is made up of a y term, an x term, and a number and are written in the form of y = mx + c. The slope of the line is known as the gradient and is represented by m in the equation. The point at which the line crosses the y-axis is the c in the equation.'
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'What is the equation for vertical lines?',
      selection: ['k = x', 'c = x', 'x = k', 'x = c'],
      answer: 'x = k',
      description: 'The equation of a vertical line always takes the form x=k. Where k is any number and k is also the x-intercept.'
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'What should the probability on each group of branches on a probability tree equal?',
      selection: ['One', 'Two', 'Three', 'Four'],
      answer: 'One',
      description: 'Sometimes you don’t know whether to multiply or add probabilities. A probability tree makes it easier to figure out when to add and when to multiply. By multiplying along the branches and adding probabilities down the columns the result should always be 1.'
    }
  ]
}

export default maths
